<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on c0d33ngr blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on c0d33ngr blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:57:55 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Invitation to participate in ECOWAS CTF Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ecowas-ctf-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:57:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ecowas-ctf-hackathon/</guid>
      
      <description>Introduction I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d be writing this. As a software developer, my world revolves around writing clean and maintainable code, collaborating with fellow software developer in the opensource communities, and also contributing to open-source softwares. But life, as they say, is full of surprises. A recent invitation to participate in ECOWAS CTF hackathon was sent to me. Since the application for my team and I to be involved was approved by the organizers, I found myself thrown me headfirst into the ever busy world of cybersecurity.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:30:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>I am an open source software developer who love solving problems and everything open source. I am interested in everything STEAM(Science, Technology, Engineering, Arts, &amp;amp; Mathematics).
I studied Electrical/Electronic Engineering Technology from Delta State Polytechnic, Ozoro, Nigeria(now known as Delta State University of Science and Technology). I am pursing a Computer Science degree from University of the People(UoPeople) which is a US distance learning school as part-time study along with MIT OpenCourseWare resources.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
