<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on c0d33ngr blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on c0d33ngr blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:38:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hng12 Task 0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hng12-task-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:38:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hng12-task-0/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;effortless-web-server-deployment-setting-up-nginx-on-aws-ec2&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Effortless Web Server Deployment: Setting Up Nginx on AWS EC2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As someone with experience in DevOps and infrastructure basics, tasks like setting up &lt;strong&gt;Nginx&lt;/strong&gt; on an &lt;strong&gt;AWS EC2&lt;/strong&gt; instance feel second nature. However, revisiting such foundational exercises offers an opportunity to refine workflows, optimize configurations, and ensure smooth deployments. Here’s a quick recap of how I approached this task and its contribution to my ongoing growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-approach-to-the-task&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Approach to the Task&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provisioning the EC2 Instance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Launching the EC2 instance was straightforward. I chose &lt;strong&gt;Ubuntu Linux&lt;/strong&gt;, a required choice for the task setups, and ensured the necessary security group rules were configured (allowing &lt;strong&gt;HTTP&lt;/strong&gt; on port 80 and &lt;strong&gt;SSH&lt;/strong&gt; on port 22).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineering Diagrams for Your Next Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/software-engineering-diagrams-for-your-next-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:27:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/software-engineering-diagrams-for-your-next-project/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software engineering is the systematic process of designing, developing, testing, and maintaining software applications to meet user requirements. To effectively communicate and understand complex software systems, software engineers rely on a variety of diagrams. These visual representations serve as blueprints, aiding in design, development, and overall project comprehension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;understanding-common-software-engineering-diagrams&#34;&gt;Understanding Common Software Engineering Diagrams&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software engineering diagrams can be categorized based on their purpose. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of the most commonly used diagram types.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invitation to participate in ECOWAS CTF Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ecowas-ctf-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:57:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ecowas-ctf-hackathon/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/ecowas-ctf-hackathon/cyber-security-1805632_640.png&#34; alt=&#34;cybersecurity image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d be writing this. As a software developer, my world revolves around writing clean and maintainable code, collaborating with fellow software developer in the opensource communities, and also contributing to open-source softwares. But life, as they say, is full of surprises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/ecowas-ctf-hackathon/ecowas-ctf-invitation.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ecowas ctf email invitation&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A recent invitation to participate in ECOWAS CTF hackathon was sent to me. Since the application for my team and I to be involved was approved by the organizers, I found myself thrown headfirst into the ever busy world of cybersecurity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:30:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/stewie_small.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;my picture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am an open source software developer who love solving problems and everything open source. I am interested in everything STEAM(Science, Technology, Engineering, Arts, &amp;amp; Mathematics).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I studied Electrical/Electronic Engineering Technology from Delta State Polytechnic, Ozoro, Nigeria(now known as Delta State University of Science and Technology).
I am pursing a Computer Science degree from University of the People(UoPeople) which is a US distance learning school as part-time study along with MIT OpenCourseWare resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
